ELEN CRISTINA FERREIRA

Surrey, BC (604) 868-7106

elen.crisf@uol.com.br

Portfolio: https://elenferreira.netlify.app/

SUMMARY

Web developer also experiences in traffic system management and manipulating map data for geoprocessing traffic engineering, improving its management and process. Had the opportunity to work with traffic systems technologies and also solved problems with public transport and individual modals besides demonstrated leadership, organization, and teamwork skills.

SKILLS

- HTML
- SASS
- SCSS
- Bootstrap
- React
- Node.js

- Gatsby
- MongoDB
- Contentful
- JavaScriptGitHub/GitBash
 - Visual Studio Code
- IntelliJ
- Eclipse
- QGIS
- AutoCAD
 - ACCESS

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

CICCC - Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

Tech Campus - Technical School

Sep 2019 - Ago 2020 - Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

• Web Development of website and landing page with HTML, SCSS styles, using React and Bootstrap libraries besides Gatsby framework and Contentful headless data.

TRANSIT MANAGER

Companhia de Engenharia de Tráfego - CET

Engineering & Management of Traffic of Sao Paulo City Mar 1996 - Jul 2019 - Sao Paulo, Brazil

- Implementations of traffic software such as geoprocessing.
- Preparation and monitoring of operational plans for large events and road works, specifically Formula 1 Grand Prix, as well as coordination and distribution of operational team activities.
- Development of traffic light projects and programming, also management with intelligent traffic lights systems.

- Preparation and monitoring of the implementation of signalling projects, such as exclusive lanes for public transport and cycle network programs in the city of Sao Paulo.
- Preparation and monitoring of civil works projects, such as the implementation of new road geometry to reduce transit accidents.

ARCHITECTURE DESIGNER

Projecto Arquitetura e Engenharia S/C Ltda.

Architecture & Engineering Projects

Nov 1992 - Mar 1996 - Itapevi, Sao Paulo, Brazil

Development of architecture projects of complex residences.

EDUCATION

Web and Mobile App Development Diploma

CICCC – Cornerstone International College

2020 - Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

- Web Development & JavaScript
- React, Node.js
- Python, Java
- Algorithms & Data Structures
- Object-oriented programming

Postgraduate Degree in Transit Planning and Management UNICESUMAR – Cesumar Center University

2018 - Maringa, Brazil

Techniques for improvement and management of traffic systems.

Master of Business Administration (MBA) in Traffic Mobility and Safety FAMESP – Faculty Method of Sao Paulo

2011 - Sao Paulo, Brazil

• Techniques for traffic planning with a focus on accident reduction.

Civil Construction Technologist Degree

FATEC-SP – Faculty of Technology of Sao Paulo

2000 - Sao Paulo, Brazil

- Civil construction
- Projects and design
- Design and structural building software